<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2022-06-06T17:01:10+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><entry><title type="html">South-Indian-Food</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2022/05/30/south-indian-food.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="South-Indian-Food" /><published>2022-05-30T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-05-30T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2022/05/30/south-indian-food</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2022/05/30/south-indian-food.html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="image" src="/assets/images/southindian.jpg" /></p>

<p>This South Indian Coconut Chickpea Curry is a spicy and super delicious curry made with white chickpeas, coconut and spices. A vegan dish.
In this recipe the real flavor comes from the coconut and whole spices. You can actually get a distinct taste of coconut. There is a subtle sweetness and this channa masala is not sour or tangy</p>

<p>The recipe posted here is a South Indian version of chickpea curry with coconut. So as the name suggests, This curry has South Indian flavors and taste awesome. basically in this recipe, all the ingredients which are commonly used in South Indian cooking are added, with grated coconut being one of the main ingredients.</p>]]></content><author><name>Dassana Amit</name></author><category term="Food" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Younster-life</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2022/05/29/younsters-life.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Younster-life" /><published>2022-05-29T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-05-29T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2022/05/29/younsters-life</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2022/05/29/younsters-life.html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="image" src="/assets/images/younsters.jpg" /></p>

<p>Youth is a worthwhile phase of one’s life. The age where the age group is no longer of a child but yet to turn out to be a grown-up is the youth age. It is an age recognized by traits of heroism, toughness, muscle, stimulation, curiosity, judgmental attitude and even much more. At this stage, even though driven by fantasy or freedom and the power to choose his or her response, all must be cautiously exercised. It is a golden phase to accomplish the dual goals of intelligence and character.</p>

<p>Youth develops a revolting personality and thus we can see conflicts in opinions between the family. It is also a major cause of worsening of family relations. Youth, being argumentative in nature, develop an attitude of apt rationale and judgment.</p>]]></content><author><name>Susanna olsson</name></author><category term="India" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[]]></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/youngsters.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/youngsters.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Cybercrime</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2022/05/28/cybercrime.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Cybercrime" /><published>2022-05-28T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-05-28T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2022/05/28/cybercrime</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2022/05/28/cybercrime.html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="image" src="/assets/images/cyber-crime.jpg" /></p>

<p>Cyber. It is the inevitable prefix that currently defines our world. From people’s privacy to inter-state relations, the term “cyber” dominates the headlines and discussions - so much so that we risk being paralyzed by the magnitude of the problems we face.</p>

<p>Despite the many remaining questions about the future of cybersecurity and governance, we must take into account that international cooperation is the key element in addressing the growing threats of cybercrime.</p>

<p>Online exploitation and abuse of girls and boys; the black cyber markets for the purchase and sale of illicit drugs and firearms; ransomware attacks and human traffickers making use of social networks to attract victims. The unprecedented scope of cybercrime - crossing borders in our homes, schools, businesses, hospitals and other vital service providers - only amplifies the threats.</p>]]></content><author><name>Yury Fedotov</name></author><category term="cyber" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Modern-india</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2022/05/27/modern-india.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Modern-india" /><published>2022-05-27T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-05-27T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2022/05/27/modern-india</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2022/05/27/modern-india.html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="image" src="/assets/images/modern-india.jpg" /></p>

<p>The history of modern constitutionalism has immortalized several events of much moment. It has, however, cast scant attention upon a great deal other episodes that merit greater engagement. Among this latter category is the making of modern India – the crafting of the constitutional text that would create the world’s largest democracy. The Indian case invites attention not merely because of its size but rather because of its conditions. This postcolonial experiment involved the coming together of democratization and constitution-making in a setting that was poor, uneducated, and divided, and one that was stepped in centuries of tradition. Unlike in the West where voting rights were expanded gradually in settings that witnessed the spread of wealth and literacy and the cementing of administrative institutions, India reversed the historically ordained process to self-rule. For India’s founders, democratic citizens were to be created through democratic practice.</p>]]></content><author><name>Madhav kohsla</name></author><category term="India" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Engineering</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2022/05/26/engineering.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Engineering" /><published>2022-05-26T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-05-26T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2022/05/26/engineering</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2022/05/26/engineering.html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="image" src="/assets/images/engineering.jpg" /></p>

<p>Engineering</p>

<p>Engineering is surely a word most people have heard of before, but have you actually ever wondered what it means to be an engineer? Most people picture brainy individuals working behind the scenes on planes and trains, but there’s so much more to this discipline than that. In the simplest terms, engineering is the act of using the scientific method to solve real-world problems, build practical machines and tools, and make the world a better place.</p>

<p>Mechanical Engineering:</p>

<p>Mechanical engineers at work
Source: industryview/iStock
Engineers in this field are definitely the kind of people who like taking things apart, learning how they work, putting them back together, and troubleshooting any problems that may arise. As such, they enjoy designing and building machines that function for specific purposes.</p>

<p>Civil Engineering:</p>

<p>Since the beginning of history, humans have engaged in civil engineering (it’s believed to be the oldest type of engineering). Simply put, civil engineering is the act of developing and maintaining buildings, roads, bridges, and dams. You know your fancy toilet? Yeah-those are pretty new in the grand scheme of things. Well, they wouldn’t exist without civil engineers who designed not only sewage systems, but water filtration systems. Without these individuals, the world would look closer to the world.</p>]]></content><author><name>Jaime Trosper</name></author><category term="Engineering" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Agricultures</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2022/05/25/agriculture.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Agricultures" /><published>2022-05-25T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-05-25T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2022/05/25/agriculture</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2022/05/25/agriculture.html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="image" src="/assets/images/agricultures.jpg" /></p>

<p>Agriculture</p>

<p>Agriculture or farming is the practice of cultivating plants and livestock. Agriculture was the key development in the rise of sedentary human civilization, whereby farming of domesticated species created food surpluses that enabled people to live in cities. The history of agriculture began thousands of years ago.</p>]]></content><author><name>Emmaline Soken-Huberty</name></author><category term="Environment" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Mechanical engineering</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2022/05/24/mechanical-engineering.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Mechanical engineering" /><published>2022-05-24T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-05-24T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2022/05/24/mechanical-engineering</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2022/05/24/mechanical-engineering.html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="image" src="/assets/images/mechanical-engineering.jpg" /></p>

<p>Mechanical engineering is the study, design, development, construction, and testing of mechanical and thermal sensors and devices, including tools, engines, and machines. Mechanical engineering careers center on creating technologies to meet a wide range of human needs.</p>]]></content><author><name>mike</name></author><category term="Engineering" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Natural-Environment</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2022/05/23/natural-environment.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Natural-Environment" /><published>2022-05-23T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-05-23T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2022/05/23/natural-environment</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2022/05/23/natural-environment.html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="image" src="/assets/images/natural-environment.jpg" /></p>

<p>The natural environment or natural world encompasses all living and non-living things occurring naturally, meaning in this case not artificial. The term is most often applied to the Earth or some parts of Earth. This environment encompasses the interaction of all living species, climate, weather and natural resources that affect human survival and economic activity.The concept of the natural environment can be distinguished as components: * Complete ecological units that function as natural systems without massive civilized human intervention, including all vegetation, microorganisms, soil, rocks, atmosphere, and natural phenomena that occur within their boundaries and their nature. * Universal natural resources and physical phenomena that lack clear-cut boundaries, such as air, water, and climate, as well as energy, radiation, electric charge, and magnetism, not originating from civilized human actions. In contrast to the natural environment is the built environment. Built environments are where humans have fundamentally transformed landscapes such as urban settings and agricultural land conversion, the natural environment is greatly changed into a simplified human environment. Even acts which seem less extreme, such as building a mud hut or a photovoltaic system in the desert, the modified environment becomes an artificial one. Though many animals build things to provide a better environment for themselves, they are not human, hence beaver dams, and the works of mound-building termites, are thought of as natural. People cannot find absolutely natural environments on Earth, and naturalness usually varies in a continuum, from 100% natural in one extreme to 0% natural in the other.</p>]]></content><author><name>Dane</name></author><category term="Environment" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Non-Veg</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2022/04/30/non-veg.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Non-Veg" /><published>2022-04-30T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-04-30T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2022/04/30/non-veg</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2022/04/30/non-veg.html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="image" src="/assets/images/non-veg.jpg" />
13 Best Non Vegetarian Recipes | Non-Veg RecipesHere are some of us for whom a good meal almost always means a meaty affair. we’ve got a list of 13 best non veg recipes that you can make at home.Plavaneeta BorahUpdated: November 30, 2021 17:56 ISTRead Time:4 min
1
13 Best Non Vegetarian Recipes | Non-Veg Recipes
Non-vegetarian recipes to prepare at home.
Non-Vegetarian Recipes- There are some of us for whom a good meal almost always means a meaty affair. With so many varied kinds of non-vegetarian dishes, one is sure to be bowled over with lip-smacking flavours. Look within the Indian sub-continent and you have unique preparations using local regions of the region. Imagine biting into Malabar fish curry, Mangalore chicken curry, Goan masala prawns, Kosha Mangsho, butter chicken, Laal Maas, Amritsari fish and Rogan Josh to name a few. Turning to International cuisines, there are many more dishes to add to the indulgence. Some of those dishes are so popular that you commonly find food fanatics dishing them out at the comfort of their kitchen. Fish and chips, steaks, barbecued pork ribs, grilled chicken, meatballs, - you name it! There is no end to the delectable non vegetarian dishes that you can enjoy to your heart’s content.</p>]]></content><author><name>Amit</name></author><category term="Food" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[13 Best Non Vegetarian Recipes | Non-Veg RecipesHere are some of us for whom a good meal almost always means a meaty affair. we’ve got a list of 13 best non veg recipes that you can make at home.Plavaneeta BorahUpdated: November 30, 2021 17:56 ISTRead Time:4 min 1 13 Best Non Vegetarian Recipes | Non-Veg Recipes Non-vegetarian recipes to prepare at home. Non-Vegetarian Recipes- There are some of us for whom a good meal almost always means a meaty affair. With so many varied kinds of non-vegetarian dishes, one is sure to be bowled over with lip-smacking flavours. Look within the Indian sub-continent and you have unique preparations using local regions of the region. Imagine biting into Malabar fish curry, Mangalore chicken curry, Goan masala prawns, Kosha Mangsho, butter chicken, Laal Maas, Amritsari fish and Rogan Josh to name a few. Turning to International cuisines, there are many more dishes to add to the indulgence. Some of those dishes are so popular that you commonly find food fanatics dishing them out at the comfort of their kitchen. Fish and chips, steaks, barbecued pork ribs, grilled chicken, meatballs, - you name it! There is no end to the delectable non vegetarian dishes that you can enjoy to your heart’s content.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Seven Wonders of the world</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2022/03/20/seven-wonders-of-the-world.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Seven Wonders of the world" /><published>2022-03-20T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-03-20T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2022/03/20/seven-wonders-of-the-world</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2022/03/20/seven-wonders-of-the-world.html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="image" src="/assets/images/seven-wonders-of-the-world.jpg" />
The Seven Wonders of The Modern World are located all over the world.  They are all very unique in their own ways.  From ruins that contain many temples and tombs, to a city that is carved out of canyon walls.  These seven architectures are some of the greatest tourist attractions in the world.  They were all given a great award to be one of the seven wonders of the world because of their beauty and history.  One should see at least one of these great wonders in their lifetime.
     Machu Picchu is located in Peru.  It is referred to as the “City of The Incas.”  Machu Picchu means “Old Mountain”, and it was built in 1450.  Many people, even the Incas had forgotten about Machu Picchu, but it was rediscovered in 1911.  Machu Picchu contains many ruins, temples, and tombs.  It is a great tourist site for Peru, and many people visit Machu Picchu every year.
     The Taj Mahal is located in India.  It is recognized as the Jewel of Muslims in India.  Taj Mahal means “Crown of Palaces.”  It began to be built in 1632, and was finished in 1653.  It is a very big palace that contains a pool and a great garden in the backyard.  It is a huge tourist attraction for India and many people visit the palace every year.</p>]]></content><author><name>Barath</name></author><category term="India" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Seven Wonders of The Modern World are located all over the world. They are all very unique in their own ways. From ruins that contain many temples and tombs, to a city that is carved out of canyon walls. These seven architectures are some of the greatest tourist attractions in the world. They were all given a great award to be one of the seven wonders of the world because of their beauty and history. One should see at least one of these great wonders in their lifetime. Machu Picchu is located in Peru. It is referred to as the “City of The Incas.” Machu Picchu means “Old Mountain”, and it was built in 1450. Many people, even the Incas had forgotten about Machu Picchu, but it was rediscovered in 1911. Machu Picchu contains many ruins, temples, and tombs. It is a great tourist site for Peru, and many people visit Machu Picchu every year. The Taj Mahal is located in India. It is recognized as the Jewel of Muslims in India. Taj Mahal means “Crown of Palaces.” It began to be built in 1632, and was finished in 1653. It is a very big palace that contains a pool and a great garden in the backyard. It is a huge tourist attraction for India and many people visit the palace every year.]]></summary></entry></feed>